[{
        "question": "What is 50% of 20?",
        "answer": "10",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "25% of a number is 5. What is the number?",
        "answer": "20",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 20% of a number is 8, what is the number?",
        "answer": "40",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 10% of 300?",
        "answer": "30",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 75% of 60?",
        "answer": "45",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "Find 5% of 80.",
        "answer": "4",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 100% of 35?",
        "answer": "35",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "Find 200% of 25.",
        "answer": "50",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "Calculate 15% of 150.",
        "answer": "22.5",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 5% of 500?",
        "answer": "25",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 75% of a number is 15, what is the number?",
        "answer": "20",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 30% of 90?",
        "answer": "27",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "Find 20% of 120.",
        "answer": "24",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "Calculate 45% of 40.",
        "answer": "18",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 25% of 48?",
        "answer": "12",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "Find 35% of 200.",
        "answer": "70",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 10% of 800?",
        "answer": "80",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "Calculate 65% of 60.",
        "answer": "39",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"

    }
]